Guide to the Thomas Merton Center Records, 1962-2009 AIS.1982.19
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- First Deposit (1982), 1971-1982; I.
  - Editorials and Statements by People (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - City Council Resolution (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Congress and the B-1 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - B-1 and Environment (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Defense Budget (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Hearing (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Arms Sales (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Conferences on B-1 and Military Budget (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Continental Walk for Disarmament (Box 9, Folder 16-18)
  - Editorials/Letters (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Pitt Paper (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - February 12 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Rockwell (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Endorsements of B-1 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Jefferson City (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Opposition to B-1 Bomber, January 1976 - June 1976 (Box 9, Folder 25-26)
  - Letters from Congress (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Minutes of B-1 Meeting (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - B-1 Letters of Endorsements (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Related Issues--Trident (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - May 12-13, Rockwell Action (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Special Reports on B-1 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Peace Conversion--Jobs Employment (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Stop B-1 Campaign--Philadelphia (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Pittsburgh B-1 Task Force (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Brochure, Merton Center (Box 10, Folder 4-7)
  - Rockwell (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Hearing--Rockwell Sit-in, May 28, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Rockwell Injunction Hearing, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - B-1 as Crime under International Law (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Nuremburg Principals (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Mary Kaufman (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Public Nuisance (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Injunctive Relief (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Press Releases -- Conference, June 15, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Conditions at Time of Sit-In (Box 10, Folder 17-18)
  - Stop B-1 Bomber (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Brief Drafts (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 21-22)
  - Rockwell and Corporations (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Stop the B-1 Bomber: Congressional Records, Pamphlets (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Outline: Brief for Injunction Hearing (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Indochina Peace Project (IPC) (Box 11, Folder 1-16)
  - International Committee to Free South Vietnam Political Prisoners (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Indochina Week of Concern, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Political Prisoners (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Medical Aid for Indochina (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Moratorium - May 4 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Vietnam (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Indochina Mobile Educational Unit (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Vietnam War (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Dikes and Dams - Documentation of American Bombing (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Vietnam and Repression (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Cambodia (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - War Crimes (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Post Indochina Commentaries (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Tiger Cage (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Tobin, S. Mary Luke (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Misc Newsclippings and Reports (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Indochina (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Rush, Molly: Papers and Collected Publications (Box 12, Folder 1-7)
  - Catholic Committee on Urban Ministry / Economic Justice (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Wounded Knee (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - National Organization of Women (NOW) / International Women's Year (Box 12, Folder 10-11)
  - Vietnam War (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Coalition to Stop Funding the War (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Assembly to Save the Peace Agreement (Washington, D.C.) (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - American Friends Service Committee (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Campaign for a Democratic Policy (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Indochina Solidarity Committee (ISC) (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Second Deposit (1993), 1971-1993; II.
  This series contains many periodicals, articles, publications, and correspondence from the 1980s that reveal the Merton Center's opposition toward President Reagan's domestic and foreign policy. Other items from this era include the River City Campaign (RCC), the Merton Center's nuclear freeze effort. The RCC organized gatherings, protests, and wrote articles and leaflets denouncing the military build-up, demanding that the money spent in defense be redirected to fight poverty. The RCC also worked to expose the large sums of money that corporations made through defense contracts. Indictments against Rockwell, Westinghouse, Nestle, and IBM are included.
  The series also documents the Merton Center's activities in opposing military intervention and aid to what they viewed as corrupt regimes in Central America. Their effort to propagate a message of peace and unity resulted in the Merton Center's establishment of a Witness for Peace program, developing an ongoing dialogue between the Nicaraguan city of San Isidro and Pittsburgh. The series houses this correspondence. Events in the 1980s were held in solidarity with the persecuted in South Africa, and the series holds records of these, as well as meeting minutes of organizations formed to protest regional job loss. At the end of the series, Boxes 25 and 26 hold periodicals from the original 1982 accession. Some of them express the progressive wing of the Catholic Church which advocates Gay rights, the Equal Rights Amendment, and Central American land reform.
  - Tri-state Conference on Manufacturing, 1991-1993 (Box 13, Folder 1-4)
  - Tri-state Conference on Steel, Pittsburgh, 1986-1992 (Box 13, Folder 5-11)
  - Steel Valley Authority, 1983-1988 (Box 13, Folder 12-14)
  - Child Care Services, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Alice in Blunderland, November 1982 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Running file hotline updates and mailings, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Anti Contra Aid Ad, February 3, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Washington office on Latin America; update - publication, 1983-1987 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Pgh. Provisional Legal Refuge Community, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Speakers, Central America, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Budget cuts/jobs with peace - leaflets, etc., 1982-83 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Deadly Connections Conference, November, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - UNTS Statement/Conference (United Nations), November, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Pax Christ. USA, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - War Toys, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Nicaragua Travel opportunities, 1984-1987 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Marches, Brigadad, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Nicaragua, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Grenada (host letter), 1983 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Press lists, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Institute for Policy Studies, 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Christic Institute, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Pamphlets on Latin America (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Latin (South) America Publications, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Economic War on Nicaragua International Treaties, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Vigil, Centra Vote, Press conference, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Refugees, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Articles from Pledge-Action (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Sanctuary, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Debt Crisis, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Moakley/Deconcini Bill, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Women's Prison Association (W.P.A.) Coalition Against the Death Penalty, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - War Crimes Tribunal, International Law/Embargo, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Lit. Table Resources, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Contra Aid, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Denominational Statements on Central America, 1983-1985 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Contra Aid Efforts, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Central America Working Group, Pledge, Etc., 1984 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Articles/clippings, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Presbyterian C.A. Literature, 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Emergency National Conference Against U.S. Military Intervention in Central America/the Caribbean, Sept. 14-16, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Various local activities, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Garth and Betsy, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Peace Pentecost, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - National Guard, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Militarization/Central America, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - National Health Rights Network (Central America), Spring 1989 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Medical Aid/Health Rights for Central America, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - That Great Ad, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Environment, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - E.N.C. Against U.S. Intervention in Central America, June 1987 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - El Salvador - labor, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Deconcini/Moakley Bill (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - "Disappeared" of Latin America (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Miguel D' Escoto, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Pittsburgh Committee for Health Rights in Central America, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Harper and Row, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Cuernavaca Center for International Dialogue on Development, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Goals and Objectives, Central America, 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Central America Emergency Response, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Central America, misc generally old (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - Office file of reports complete C.C.A., 1983 (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Costa Rica, 1987-1990 (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Legislative Action Nicaragua, 1986, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - Budget, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - April 20 Mobilization, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Americas Watch March, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - Neighbor to Neighbor, Central American Coffee, 1990-1992 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Central America Week, 1984, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 2-3)
  - Central America Series, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Chammore Gov. Nicaragua, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Chile, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Churches and El Salvador, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Cispes, 1988-1990 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Comadres/Winds, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Contra Aid Overview, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Central America Conference Registration, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Central America Conference, March, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Contra Watch, 1987-88 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Contra Aid, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Pittsburgh Area Peace and Justice Groups updated, November 7, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Computer membership lists, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Democratic Party platform hearings, May 14, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - El Salvador, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - El Salvador, news clippings, 1986-1990 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Eye Witness Week, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Fast for Justice and Peace in the Americas, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Indians of Central America, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Peace tax fund, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Poetry, June 4, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - McGinnis Conference, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Nicaragua Newsclippings, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Religious response, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Martyrs of El Salvador, November 16, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Options for peace in Central America, undated (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Joe Regotti, long term witness for peace, Summer 1986 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Sanctuary/Central America, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Peace Plan, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - "Romero", 1989 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Sanctuary C.A., undated (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Nicaragua Network, Sanctuary, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Brian Wilson, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Witness for Peace, 1984-1988 (Box 15, Folder 37-38)
  - El Salvador, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 1-2)
  - Witness for Peace, Nicaragua, 1983-1985 (Box 16, Folder 3-4)
  - Central America Mobilization Coalition (CAMC), 1988 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Central America Newsline, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Central America Mobilization Coalition Newsletter, Focus, January-February 1984 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Central America Report, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Central America, November 28, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Council of Protestant Churches of Nicaragua who Aid the Poor (CEPAD) Report, 1989-1992 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Central America Historical Inst., 1988 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - News articles on C.A., 1988 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Central Intelligence Agency (CIA), John Stockwell, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Committee in Solidarity with People of El Salvador (CISPES) Brochure (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Coalition for a New Foreign and Military Policy, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Options for peace in Central America, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - The New People, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - IBM Shareholders Mtg. South Africa, April 24, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Co-op America (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Building Peace, U.S. Catholic Conference, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Latin American Studies Association, 1979, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Quest for Peace - Quixote Center, 1987-1990 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Pledge of Resistance (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Refugee Rights, 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Roger Schrading (in El Salvador), 1986-1989 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Spanish Translations, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Vosh, 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Travel to Nicaragua, 1987-1989 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Oxfam America News, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Trips to Central America, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Trish Beatty, Sr. City Info., 1988 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Local Witness For Peace (WFP) Files, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 32-36)
  - Attacks by the Nicaraguan Contras, 1983-1988 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Misc. Items, 1984-1990 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - National Packet, April 20, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Nicaragua Elections, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Center for National Security Studies (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Miscellaneous Items (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Academic Consortium for Cooperation and Conflict Resolution (ACCCR), 1979-1982 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Bread for the World, 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Center Peace, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Center of Concern - Center focus, 1984-1987 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Coalition for Freedom for Southern Africa (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Coalition for Our Common Future, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Confluence, 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Discussion Group, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Draft Counseling, undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Gorbachev at U.N., 1988 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Gorbachev Proposals, Test Ban, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Lithuania, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Hunger Action Coalition, 1982-1986 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Jobs, Peace, Justice, PA Caucus, December 15, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Just Harvest, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Church Statements, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - International Women's Day, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Nagasaki Day, August 9, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Jan Neffke, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Pittsburghers Against Apartheid (PAA), 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Network Calendar Items, 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - No to NATO, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Charles Parry, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Pittsburgh Committee for a Comprehensive Peace in the Middle East (PCCPME), 1991 (Box 17, Folder 24-25)
  - Rush, Molly, 1979-1987 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Peace Pilgrim, undated (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Peace Pentecost DC, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Reagan Ranches Outreach, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Rockwell International Shareholders Action, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Fred Rogers, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - What to Tell the Children, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Salvation Army, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Peace Links, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Solidarity, November 10, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Physicians for Social Responsibility (PSR) Conference, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Clarence Thomas, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - SDI/Star Wars, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 1-3)
  - International Peace Communication and Coordination Center, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Articles on Peace/Nuclear Issue, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Human Costs of the Cold War, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Intermediate Range Nuclear Forces (INF) Treaty, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Nov. 19 Vigil, Reagan/Gorbachev Summit, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Arms Race, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - B-1 Stealth, 1988-1990 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Curl Defense, 1977-1983 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - The Button, Daniel Ford, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Conventional Forces in Europe, 1988-1990 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Deterrence (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Nuclear Strategy, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Summitry, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Reykjavik, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Ramparts Press (social issues, politics), 1982-1986 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - World War III, 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Sane, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Space Shuttle, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Star Wars and Europe, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Star Wars opinion, local, 1985-1989 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - First strike weapons, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - MX (missile-experimental), 1979-1989 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Nuclear Warfighting, 1986-1988 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Nuclear Winter, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Psychic numbing - psychological effects of the bomb, 1982-1988 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Weapons test errors, 1987-1990 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - First strike, 1983-1985 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Discriminate deterrence, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Disarmament, 1974-1981 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Strategic Arms Limitation Talks (SALT) II, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - East Europe, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Misc. names, addresses, and numbers, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Activity forms, Peace Festival, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Peace Festival, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - What's Happening to Our Country, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Booklets, c. 1980 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Peace Festival, Kita exhibit, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 6-10)
  - Lobbying material, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Peace TV, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Test Ban, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Resources, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Bethel Park Comm. Coalition, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Peace Festival, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 16-20)
  - Peace Art/literature, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Nuclear Free Zone, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Avg. Events, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Resolution No. 665, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - August events, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Goals sheets, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Federal Budget, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Floating Peace Lantern (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Zabelka, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Lenten booklet, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Charlie King, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Hard Times Banquet, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Film Festival, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Marcia Taylor Concert, November 13, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Gumbleton, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Advent Booklet, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Membership Event, November 1985 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Jim Douglas, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Pax Christi USA, 1984-1990 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - USS Pittsburgh, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Regional Retreat, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Libya, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Hungry for Profit, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Heinz, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Three Mile Island (TMI) Train, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - New Person Award, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Peace Pentecost, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Plowshares Eight, 1980, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Letter to President Reagan, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Liturgies, 1970-1973 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Staff/team/board meetings, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Newsletter Originals, 1984-1987 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Resources, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Hiba Kusha, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - The Hunger Project, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Parishes, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Association of Pgh. Priests, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Talks/presentations to community groups, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - For the Sake of the People Liturgy (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - St. Raphael, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Sacred Heart, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Birthday Liturgy (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Catechetical Conference, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Central America, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Special Programs, undated (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Denominational Ministry Strategy (DMS), 1985 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Foot washing, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Investor Responsibility Research Center (IRRC), 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - River City Campaign (RCC), 1985 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Renewals, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Sane, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Staff, 1985-1988 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - CM budget, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Tri State phone tree, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Youth comp., 1985 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Phone Tree update (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Phone Tree Work, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Advent Epiphany Inserts/Christmas Bulletins, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Clusters, Mon. Valley, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Merton Events Program, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Newsletters, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Mobilization for Survival, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - El Salvador, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Phone-a-thon, Lists, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - The Exchange Project, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Women's Issues, 1975-1978 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Miscellaneous, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Abolition/Ban the Bomb, 1979-1982 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Arms Control, 1978-1981 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Arms Race Threat, 1979-1981 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Arms Sales, 1976-1980 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Brandywine Peace Community, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Chemical/Biological Warfare, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Civil Defense, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - CIA, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Clergy and Laity Concerned Report, 1985-1988 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Cold War Revival, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Cruise Missiles, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Euromissile Reading Packet (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Economics of Arms Race, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Misc. Important Statements, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Indochina Resource Center, 1972-1976 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Jobs with Peace, 1985, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 16-17)
  - Military Contractors, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Mobilization for Survival, 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Fast Nonviolent Tactics Development Project, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - MX Missile, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - National No Nukes Prison Support Newsletter, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Neutron Bomb, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - No More War Toys, 1987-1989 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Nuclear Power/Bomb Proliferation, 1979-1981 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Nuclear Free Pacific, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Nuclear Freeze Campaign, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Nuclear Pittsburgh, 1978-1979 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Nuclear Times, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Peace Conversion, 1979-1981 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Physicians for Social Responsibility (PSR), 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Pope John Paul II, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Plowshares Eight, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Progressive on H Bomb, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Pro-Lifers for Survival, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Pointer's Union, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Reagan Administration, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Reagan Rally, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Religious/Task Force, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Resistance, 1978-1980 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Sojourners, 1983-1985 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - War Resisters League, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - W. Pa. Coalition for Corporate Responsibility, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Working for Peace and Prosperity, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Zabelka Video Flyers, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Africa Day, Mandela, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Africa Focus Project, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - South Africa, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 3)